greenknightmethod.com 2011-10-03

# Privacy Policy | Green Knight Method

This is the privacy policy for this website. By using this site, you imply consent to the privacy policy and information collection practices of this site.

**Information Collected**  
Our web server does not automatically recognize or store your email address of any other personally identifiable information. If we do collect email addresses, it is always with the users consent, and done via a double opt-in process, which is the current best practice model in the industry and in full compliance with CANSPAM laws.

**Usage Tracking**  
The only information we currently collect is aggregate information about how visitors navigate and interact with the website. This information does not uniquely identify visitors, but only tracks group usage habits, such as the number of pages visited, average time on site, and so on. We do not use that tracking information for anything but the use described above.

**Cookies**  
In some cases, we use cookies to track user behavior so we can provide a better user experience. Please be aware that if you block cookies for this site, navigation and usability will likely be diminished. Please note that these cookies do not harm your computer in any way. They do not contain any malicious code of any kind, such as adware, spyware or any other type of malware. They are similar to web standard session cookies that are used on many websites at this time.

**Secure Ordering**  
All purchases through this website are made on PayPal's secure server.

**Policy Changes**  
If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our web site periodically.

**Contact**  
If you feel that this site is not following its stated privacy policy, or if you have any questions or comments about this policy, you may contact us [here](http://www.greenknightmethod.com/contact.php).
